ADDIN IQRA RUDY

FREELANCER





^ +60 19-2941400



addiniq12@gmail.com



2 39, Jalan Bendahara 10/6, Taman Bendahara

SKILLS

- Unreal Engine 4 Intermediate Level
- Designing Game Environment Intermediate Level
- Script Writing Intermediate Level
- Social Media Management Intermediate Level
- Animating Novice Level
- Video Editing Intermediate Level
- Isometric Design Intermediate Level
- Writing Skills Intermediate Level

LANGUAGES

- Bahasa Melayu (Native Speaker)
- English (Intermediate Level)
- French (Novice Level)

EDUCATION

SPM

SMK KUALA SELANGOR (ACCOUNTING STREAM) 2015-2019

DIPLOMA IN NEW MEDIA COMMUNICATION AND CONTENTPRENEURSHIP(MC111)

UiTM Kampus Alor Gajah

2020-present

PROFILE

Greetings, I'm Addin Iqra Bin Rudy. I 'm a highly motivated person and love doing creative works. I'm into video editing, copywriting, isometric design, graphic design, game development, digital content, social media management and photography. Passionate about learning about them and gaining new experiences and knowledges.

EXPERIENCE

Argania Clarent Bougas (Content Creator) - Assignment NMC251 2021-2022

Rompong Hyper (Social Media Manager) - Assignment COM205 2021-2022

Nominee for GameINC22 Top 5 Best Trailer (Timmy's Dream)

EXTRACURRICULUR

TECHNICAL TEAM BUREAU LENSA 2022

GAMEINC 2022

PLAYER SUPRO E-SPORT 2021

DKLS LINGUISTIC AMBASSADOR AWARD -ESSAY WRITING COMPETITION WITH ELS LANGUAGE CENTRES 2019

DIPLOME D'ETUDE EN LANGUE FRANCAISE DELF A1

REFERENCES

MISS WAN ASFAROZZA



+60 13-380 7870

MADAM HAJAR ABDUL AZIZ



+60 13-670 0477